The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Snow is the sign of a good harvest !
Take it, take it.
Brother, come by my house !
Sure.
Happy New Year !
Uncle Wang !
How did you know we were coming ?
Happy New Year.
Brother Wang,
are you busy ?
I'm free.
Let's talk inside.
This is the first time
that I've seen him act like this.
He must need help for something.
Brother Ceng,
sit down.
If you have anything to ask, go ahead.
It's fine, it's fine...
It's only borrowing some silver.
What's so embarrassing about it ?
Oh you...
wait until we are home.
Fine,
since Father won't speak, then I will.
Mother wants to buy the shop next to ours
to make our shop bigger,
but we don't have enough money.
We want to borrow.
Brother Wang,
my wife thinks
that our shop is too small
and that it limits our business.
She saw that old Li's shop is for rent
so she wanted it immediately.
How much do you need ?
The shop is pretty big
and we have to pay 2 years of rent at once...
It would be...
50 taels of silver.
30 taels is enough.
Mother clearly said 80.
I don't need this much !
Brother Wang,
I only want to borrow 30 taels of silver.
Brother Ceng,
I'm not lending you this money.
This is Da Niu's New Year's money
and it's also money for wine.
I'd like to buy a jug of wine every day.
From now on,
This money is worth 10 years of fruit wine.
Brother Wang...
This...
Thank you, Uncle Wang !
This is the first time I've recieved so much at New Year !
This kid...
Thank you.
Get up, Brother Ceng.
What's 10 years or 8 years ?
From now on, as long as you live here,
I'll send you a jug of this wine every day !
I'll deliver it to Uncle Wang.
Deal.
Goodbye Uncle Wang !
It's cold ouside,
let's go back quickly.
The 400 years of killing intent
have been condensed into 4 beads.
If I want to understand the heavens,
I have to completely embrace
the life of a mortal
for a lifetime.
6 years later
If Teng Huayuan was still alive,
he would never recognize
that this mortal
and the all-powerful Wang Lin
are the same person.
Excuse me.
Don't worry.
Please.
Uncle Wang said
that he had parents and a wife.
But for the past 6 years,
he's been all alone...
Uncle Wang !
You're finally here.
If you don't come over by youself,
then I must invite you.
Here.
Thank you, Uncle Wang.
Brother Wang,
this is your favorite beef sauce.
Eat more during the New Year.
This beef is good for the stomach
but you have to eat it with wine !
Cheers !
This is the money you lent us before.
I want to return some of it.
I told you before, it's for buying wine.
No need to return it.
Brother,
you're an honest person.
Without your help,
we wouldn't be where we are today.
We will always take you in as our family.
We want to pay you back little by little,
this is to show our goodwill.
My family
will never take advantage of you.
That's right, Brother Wang.
Uncle Wang,
don't worry.
Although it's not as good as yours,
our business is also doing well.
Let's go...
Happy New Year !
The market opened early this year !
Boss, business is flourishing !
Shopkeeper Wang,
Happy New Year.
Please come in.
I don't have silver for tips.
No matter how friendly you are.
Look at what you're saying.
The manager has ordered that
the first seat by the east window
is always reserved for you.
Shopkeeper Wang,
this wine comes from overseas.
Please try it.
Manager Li,
I'm not here to collect rent
so you can relax.
Business is not good lately.
I spent a lot of money hiring this troupe to perform.
Without you,
and the 20 taels of gold you lent us last year,
our theater would have been closed.
This little lady sure sings well.
She lured me here from the north of the city.
It's him...
Gooood !
What is this beggar doing here ? Go away !
I don't have money today.
You dare to touch me ?
If you touch me again,
I'll lie down here and never get up !
I'm here to listen to the music !
For the sake of the New Year,
I'll give you money.
Now go away.
Damn it.
It's a real one !
It's harder than gold.
It's your manager's idea.
A pot of tea.
Forget it.
Shopkeeper Wang is kind.
I'll let you off the hook today.
Thank you.
If no one guides you,
I'm afraid you will never reach Soul Formation.
What a pity, how pitiful...
It's you !
Senior,
We haven't met in 7 years, you still look the same.
You became a mortal ?
You really turned into a mortal !
Good wine !
I've seen countless cutivators forming their soul in my life.
But you are the first one to be able to turn mortal
in just 6 years.
Not bad.
It's not that
your flesh and blood are similar to a mortal
but your soul is.
Young man,
if you can experience a domain
I promise that you will
reach Soul Formation
within 100 years.
What is a domain ?
Look,
I'm getting old.
When I get hungry,
I can't remember anything.
But if you treat me to a meal,
I'll tell you everything I remember.
Senior, take your time to enjoy the performance.
Junior is leaving.
Interesting...
Not bad.
So this the place
where you're turning mortal ?
Flood Dragon !?
Flame Spider
Heaven Noise Beast
Zhong Gu
Eight-clawed Beast
Ti Lun !?
Not bad, young man.
You managed to bring most of the beasts
from the Sea of Devils here.
I really underestimated you.
I never would have thought that you had such experience.
You wouldn't have been able to make these carvings
of Soul Formation cultivators and Desolate beasts
if you hadn't fought them personally.
What's your name ?
Wang Lin
I can't see through his cultivation.
He's probably higher than Soul Formation.
Senior,
my old house
cannot withstand your power.
Please restrain yourself.
Kid,
experience it for a bit.
This is a domain.
This is my Raging Domain.
I used this domain back then
to reach Soul Formation.
Under this domain,
all spiritual energy and even your Nascent Soul
will be assimilated
and fall under my control.
A domain...
So this is the power of a domain...
Senior,
why have none of the Soul Formation cultivators I met before
displayed this kind of domain ?
My bad, I forgot.
I lowered my cultivation to Soul Formation
but my domain upgraded at Soul Transformation
so it was a little too powerful.
Soul Formation cultivators don't display their domains.
Only a sliver of it
is present in their spells.
It's hard to detect.
Based on your past achievements,
if you experience more domains, you will break past Nascent Soul.
What do you think ?
How about I help you reach Soul Formation ?
Senior, why are you helping me ?
Well...
I can tell that these carvings are pretty good.
This...
Okay,
I can give you all of these.
What would I want your low quality carvings for ?
Only those half finished carvings are worth looking at
but I have no use for them.
Look...
I'm handsome, bright and dominating.
Did I move your heart ?
Don't you think
I would make a very good model for a carving ?
Okay.
But my cultivation isn't high enough yet.
I failed making Soul Formation carvings,
not to mention a Senior like you.
Only after I reach Soul Formation,
can I make your carving perfect.
There's no rush.
You must make it perfect.
I want a nude carving too, you must make it perfect !
And you've got to make more than one.
I want a hundred !
I will give my carvings to all the beautiful ladies.
We need to hurry up.
Hurry up ? For what ?
To have you experience more domains of course.
So you can reach Soul Formation.
A teleportation of 100 000 li ?!
Late stage Nascent Soul
can only teleport up to 1000 li.
Can a Soul Transformation cross 100 000 ?
What's his cultivation level ?
I'm getting old,
my body is a lot worse than it used to be.
This teleportation
only moved us 100 000 li.
I'm ashamed.
Kid,
have you seen someone teleport this distance before ?
No.
After seeing how powerful I am,
you don't even let out a fart ?
Senior's cultivation
is something Junior has never seen before.
I admire you !
That's the White Cloud Sect.
Let's go, this old man will take you to trash that sect.
Senior,
are we just going like this ?
Wear this.
Unless someone is two full levels above you,
they won't be able to see your appearance.
This is something I've saved for a long time.
You must return it to me when we're done.
This hat looks ordinary
but it has countless restrictions on it.
The essence of these restrictions
is comparable to ancient restrictions.
What an overbearing technique.
Goldy,
smash !
The formation of a rank 4 country,
was broken in a single blow.
That's it ? Disappearing already ?
I fed you so many artifacts
and put effort in you every day !
Yet you're too lazy to play around ?
Who destroyed the formation ?
This sect is worthy of a rank 4 country.
There are more
than 30 Nascent Souls cultivators.
And those 5 are Soul Formation.
Wen Baoxin
White Cloud Sect Leader
Soul Formation
The two of you broke my White Cloud Sect's formation.
If you don't explain this
then you are dead.
I don't care,
I'm just a hired hand.
He asked me to come,
talk to him.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.